in may twenty twenty five
在五月二十五
we got a first hand look at what a missile defense
我们得到了导弹防御系统的第一手资料
system looks like during a major international conflict
系统看起来像在重大国际冲突中
when Israel attacked Iran out of the
当以色列从
blue and prompted a retaliation
蓝色并引发报复
this system is often called the iron dome
这个系统通常被称为铁穹
but the iron dome is actually the lowest and
但是铁穹实际上是最低的
cheapest level of this missile defense system
这种导弹防御系统最便宜的水平
consisting of ten batteries costing
由十个电池组成
around one hundred million dollars each
每个大约一亿美元
with each missile it fires costing
每发射一枚导弹都要花钱
around forty thousand dollars
大约四万美元
which is actually incredibly cheap in comparison to
与相比，这实际上非常便宜
the four million dollar interceptors used in the
价值四百万美元的拦截器
United States Patriot missile defense batteries
美国爱国者导弹防御系统
and recently
最近
the United States began planning to
美国开始计划
imitate the marketing of this system
模仿这个系统的营销
branding their own system the golden dome
将自己的系统命名为金色穹顶
but there is a problem
但有一个问题
this is a Kassam rocket
这是一枚Kassam火箭
the most common rocket fired out of Gaza
加沙最常见的火箭
it's a small rocket that runs on sugar
这是一个靠糖运行的小火箭
and potassium nitrate fertilizer
和硝酸钾肥料
and this is a hypersonic glide vehicle
这是一个高超音速滑翔飞行器。
one cost eight hundred dollars and was developed by
一个花了八百美元，是由
impoverished people within the confines of the walls of
城墙内的贫困人民
Gaza meant to travel unguided a mere sixteen kilometers
加沙本来只需要16公里
the other can fly from anywhere in the world
另一个可以从世界任何地方飞过来
reach the limits of space
达到空间的极限
guide itself back down and
引导自己后退
maneuver inside earth's atmosphere
在地球大气层内机动
dodging attacks and guiding itself with an incredible
躲避攻击，用不可思议的
degree of accuracy to its target halfway across the earth
精确到地球另一端的目标
the high cost of the iron dome system would pale in
铁穹系统的高成本将在
comparison to a system meant to defend against these larger
与旨在防御这些更大的系统相比
more sophisticated threats
更复杂的威胁
the need for this defense system is hard to justify
这种防御系统的需要很难被证明是合理的
considering the us has never had to defend
考虑到美国从未需要防御
itself from missile attacks on its own soil
免受导弹袭击
so  what is the golden dome system
那么什么是金穹顶系统
how will it work
它将如何工作？
and how much can it truly protect a
它能在多大程度上真正保护一个
country as big as the United States
和美国一样大的国家
the golden dome is expected to counter a wide range of
金色穹顶预计将对抗广泛的
advanced threats including ballistic missiles
包括弹道导弹在内的高级威胁
hypersonic glide vehicles and cruise missiles
高超音速滑翔飞行器和巡航导弹
the project is expected to cost anywhere between one
该项目预计成本介于
hundred and sixty one billion and five hundred and forty
一千六百一十五百四十
two billion over a twenty year period equivalent to six to
20亿在20年的时间里相当于6
twenty seven years of nasa's entire operating budget
NASA 27年的全部运营预算
so how do systems like this work
那么这样的系统是如何工作的呢？
the iron Dome was designed to
铁穹顶旨在
intercept rockets and artillery
拦截火箭炮
at the heart of the system is a self contained radar
系统的核心是一个独立的雷达
capable of detecting and tracking a wide range of threats
能够检测和跟踪广泛的威胁
when a threat is detected
当检测到威胁时
the radar sends the data to a
雷达将数据发送到
battle management and control unit
战斗管理和控制单元
which quickly calculates the projectile's trajectory
可以快速计算出弹丸的弹道
if the system determines that it's headed towards a
如果系统确定它正朝着一个
populated area or a critical infrastructure
人口稠密地区或关键基础设施
it responds with a tamir interceptor
它用泰米尔拦截器回应
which guides itself to the target using the
它使用
ground radar data and its own optical sensor
地面雷达数据和自己的光学传感器
it's common to call the entire
通常称之为整个
missile defense system the iron dome
导弹防御系统铁穹
but it's just the last part of a multi layered system
但这只是多层次系统的最后一部分
the iron Dome only covers the lowest altitude layer
铁穹顶只覆盖最低海拔层
with David sling handling medium range
大卫吊索处理中等范围
threats and the arrow system managing high
威胁和箭头系统管理高
altitude long range ballistic missiles
高空远程弹道导弹
it's this arrow system that is currently under incredible
正是这个箭头系统目前处于难以置信的状态
strain as Iran retaliates to israel's attacks with some
伊朗对以色列的袭击进行报复
missiles getting through as the system is being overwhelmed
导弹通过，因为系统不堪重负
and with interceptor missiles running low
随着拦截导弹越来越少
this could get worse
这可能会变得更糟
with reports that it's costing Israel two hundred and
有报道说它花费了以色列200万
eighty five million dollars a day to keep the system
每天八千五百万美元来维持这个系统
operational  with the arrow system interceptors
使用箭系统拦截器
costing three million dollars each
每张价值三百万美元
one of Iran's newer missiles is called the fatah
伊朗的一种新型导弹叫做法塔赫
they label it a hypersonic ballistic missile
他们称之为高超音速弹道导弹
but that's a bit of an overstatement
但这有点夸大其词
the hypersonic description of missiles usually refers to
导弹的高超音速描述通常是指
the highly maneuverable rockets that fly low in the
高度机动的火箭在
atmosphere and are able to shift direction mid flight
大气层，能够在飞行中改变方向
the fatta by contrast follows a high
相比之下，脂肪遵循高
arc like a ballistic missile
就像弹道导弹
it does reach hypersonic speeds on re entry
它在重返大气层时确实达到了高超音速
but so do most ballistic missiles
但大多数弹道导弹也是如此
the fatr can maneuver slightly
法特可以稍微移动
but it's not on the same level as
但它与
a hypersonic glide vehicle
高超音速滑翔飞行器
the real challenge comes from numbers
真正的挑战来自数字
Iran's strategy is to overwhelm the missile defense system
伊朗的战略是压倒导弹防御系统
by launching one hundred to four hundred missiles at once
一次发射100到400枚导弹
along with waves of cheaper drones
随着廉价无人机的浪潮
that clutter radar systems
使雷达系统混乱
the iron dome also has the advantage that it's defending
铁穹也有它防御的优势
a small country where cities are close together
城市相近的小国
the missiles and attacks that could be
导弹和袭击可能是
launched against the us are much more complex
针对美国的发射要复杂得多
than anything launched against Israel
比任何针对以色列的东西都多
in the event of a war
一旦发生战争
the us will need to defend against
美国将需要防御
long range ballistic missiles
远程弹道导弹
intercontinental threats
洲际威胁
and increasingly hypersonic weapons
和越来越多的高超音速武器
the executive order lays out an ambitious plan
行政命令提出了一个雄心勃勃的计划
it goes beyond building a single defensive wall
它不仅仅是建造一堵防御墙
aiming instead to create multiple layers of
相反，旨在创建多层
protection for the Continental United States
保护美国大陆
each layer is designed to handle different types of
每一层都旨在处理不同类型的
threats working together to stop attacks from every angle
威胁联手从各个角度阻止袭击
parts of the plan focus on upgrading existing missile
该计划的一部分集中在升级现有导弹上
defense systems and integrating them into a unified strategy
防御系统并将其整合为统一战略
other sections propose bold and controversial
其他部分提出了大胆而有争议的建议
new ideas that could reshape how the us
可能重塑美国如何
approaches missile defense for decades to come
未来几十年接近导弹防御系统
a missile's flight is split into three key phases
导弹的飞行分为三个关键阶段
it starts with the boost phase
它从助推阶段开始
this phase is short
这个阶段很短
just a few minutes before the missile reaches space
就在导弹到达太空前几分钟
then comes the mid course phase where
然后是中间阶段
the missile travels through space
导弹穿越太空
this is the longest and trickiest part
这是最长也是最棘手的部分
some missiles drop decoys or multiple warheads
一些导弹投掷诱饵或多枚弹头
and some can even change direction
有些甚至可以改变方向
and defense systems have to figure
防御系统必须弄清楚
out what's real and what's not
什么是真实的什么不是
the final stretch is the terminal phase
最后阶段是最后阶段
the warheads plunge back into the atmosphere
弹头就会坠入大气层
racing towards their targets
奔向目标
there's only a few seconds to react
只有几秒钟的反应时间
one mistake and it's too late
一个错误就太晚了
before any interceptor can be launched
在任何拦截器发射之前
the system has to know a missile is coming
系统必须知道导弹要来了
that starts with detection
这从检测开始
one of the clear signs is the heat from the
一个明显的迹象是来自
missile's engines during the boost phase
助推阶段的导弹引擎
this intense heat can be seen by infrared sensors in space
太空中的红外传感器可以看到这种高温
the job of watching for these launches falls to the space
监视这些发射的工作落在了太空
based infrared system operated by the us space force
由美国太空部队操作的基于红外系统
it uses a network of satellites in
它使用卫星网络
geosynchronous orbit and highly elliptical orbits
地球同步轨道和高度椭圆轨道
these orbits give the satellites persistent
这些轨道使卫星具有持久性
coverage over key regions of the planet
覆盖全球重点地区
especially high latitude areas that are harder to monitor
尤其是高纬度地区更难监控
once a missile is detected
一旦发现导弹
the next critical step is to track its path in real time
下一个关键步骤是实时跟踪它的路径
by watching how it moves
通过观察它是如何移动的
defense systems can quickly figure out where it's going
防御系统可以迅速找出它的去向
decide if it's a threat
决定这是否是威胁
and send interceptors to the right place to stop it
并派拦截器到正确的地方阻止它
this tracking relies on a mix of sensors
这种跟踪依赖于混合传感器
some in space
太空中的一些
others on the ground
地上的其他人
each plays a role using different
每个人都扮演着不同的角色
technologies to follow the missile speed
跟踪导弹速度的技术
altitude and direction
高度和方向
as the missile progresses through its
随着导弹通过其
midcourse and terminal phases
中段和末段
ground based Radar systems join in on tracking
地面雷达系统加入跟踪
there are radar stations scattered all over the world
有遍布世界各地的雷达站
but one stands out most
但有一个最突出
this is the long range discrimination radar
这是远程分辨雷达
this futuristic looking phased array Radar is
这种看起来很未来的相控阵雷达
located in clear space force station Alaska
位于阿拉斯加清晰太空部队站
strategically located for maximum field of
战略性地定位于最大的领域
view in the direction of expected attacks
按预期攻击方向查看
phased array radar like those used in the f
像f中使用的相控阵雷达
thirty five have hundreds of tiny antennas
35个有数百个小天线
we can see metal plates set in rows in the
我们可以看到金属板排成一排
f thirty five phased array antenna
f三十五相控阵天线
the metal plates have slots cut into them
金属板上有切槽
and each and every one of these slots is an antenna
这些插槽中的每一个都是天线
one thousand six hundred in total
总共一千六百
this allows the phased array antenna to steer its Radar
这使得相控阵天线能够控制它的雷达
using constructive and destructive interference
使用相长干涉和相消干涉
it also allows the Radar to track multiple objects
它还允许雷达跟踪多个物体
by splitting the Radar into smaller subsections or
通过将雷达分成更小的子部分或
combining them into one huge radar when needed
在需要时将它们组合成一个巨大的雷达
this radar in Alaska is made from gallium nitride because
阿拉斯加的雷达是由氮化镓制成的，因为
it can handle a huge amount of power running through it
它可以处理大量的能量
while conducting the heat it produces away quickly
当传导热量时，它会迅速产生热量
this material has even made its
这种材料甚至使其
way into electronic chargers
进入电子充电器
allowing them to be much smaller
让它们变得更小
doing away with the massive power bricks of old
取消旧的巨大动力砖
while enabling incredibly fast charging
同时实现令人难以置信的快速充电
but in this case it makes for a more efficient
但在这种情况下，它使更有效
radar with longer range and higher resolution
射程更远、分辨率更高的雷达
this is incredibly important because in the
这是非常重要的，因为在
mid course phase of a missile's trajectory
导弹弹道的中段
they often deploy decoys
他们经常部署诱饵
which can be as low tech as nuts and
这可能像坚果一样低技术
bolts to distract and confuse radar
分散和混淆雷达的螺栓
this Radar in Alaska is designed to operate
阿拉斯加的这种雷达设计用于
at both lower and higher frequency
以较低和较高的频率
allowing it to track at longer ranges at low
允许它以低速度在更远的范围内跟踪
frequencies and switch to higher frequencies
并切换到更高的频率
to increase the Radar resolution
提高雷达分辨率
allowing it to better discern
让它更好地辨别
between decoys from actual threats
在实际威胁的诱饵之间
this is just one of many radars integrated into
这只是集成到
the space force's missile defense system with
太空部队的导弹防御系统
others like the massive floating radar operating
其他像大型浮动雷达运行
out of Honolulu on a self propelled platform
从火奴鲁鲁的自行平台上
once a missile has been detected and tracked
一旦导弹被探测和跟踪
the final and most critical step is interception
最后也是最关键的一步是拦截
these interceptors don't use explosives but
这些拦截器不使用炸药但是
kinetic energy to destroy the warheads
摧毁弹头的动能
and for good reason
并且有充分的理由
first  an explosion could potentially detonate the warhead
首先爆炸可能会引爆核弹头
which could be nuclear
可能是核弹
chemical or even biological
化学甚至生物
the goal is to rip the warhead to shreds and disable it
目标是把弹头撕成碎片并使其失效
next  these interceptions can occur at very high altitude
接下来这些拦截会发生在非常高的高度
where there is little to no air
那里几乎没有空气
where explosives would be less effective
炸药不太有效的地方
not because of the lack of oxygen
不是因为缺氧
explosives have all of the oxidizer they
炸药有所有的氧化剂
need in their chemical structure
需要它们的化学结构
that's what makes them explosive
这就是它们爆炸的原因
but because explosions need air to propagate the blast wave
但是因为爆炸需要空气来传播冲击波
the explosion would only be effective if it was
爆炸只有在
within range of the shrapnel or the thermal blast
在弹片或热力爆炸的范围内
which is incredibly hard to time when your target
当你的目标
is veering and steering at hypersonic speeds
以高超音速转向和转向
so a massive hailstorm of hypersonic debris
所以高超音速碎片的巨大冰雹
is the chosen method of destruction
是选择的毁灭方法
for this to happen
让这一切发生
the interceptor needs a way to
拦截器需要一种方法
track and detect its target too
跟踪和检测它的目标
older systems used a spinning disk with
旧系统使用旋转磁盘
alternating dark and light stripes
深浅条纹交替
this disk spun in front of an infrared detector
这个圆盘在红外探测器前旋转
as the target's infrared signature
作为目标的红外信号
passes through the rotation pattern
通过旋转模式
it creates a fluctuating signal
它会产生波动信号
if the target was off center
如果目标偏离中心
the signal pulsed in and out of phase with the spin
信号随自旋的相位变化
the signal would only remain steady
信号只会保持稳定
when the target was centered
当目标居中时
modern systems use an array of sensitive
现代系统使用一系列敏感的
photodiodes that work more like a camera
更像相机的光电二极管
these detectors are made from indium antimonide
这些探测器是由锑化铟制成的
a material sensitive to infrared
对红外线敏感的材料
they produce a black and white thermal image
它们产生黑白热图像
allowing the missile to lock onto the target
让导弹锁定目标
all of these steps can be neatly
所有这些步骤都可以整齐地
packed into a single system too
也打包到一个系统中
like the Aegis system that is deployed
就像部署的宙斯盾系统一样
on us navy destroyers and cruisers
美国海军驱逐舰和巡洋舰
aegis's land based equivalent is tadd
神盾的陆基等价物是tadd
and all of these systems share information and create a
所有这些系统共享信息并创建一个
digital 3d battlefield map over the entire planet
覆盖整个星球的数字3d战场地图
incorporating data from every sensor
合并来自每个传感器的数据
possible whether it be from satellites
可能是来自卫星
planes or radar
飞机或雷达
and this data can even be fed into an f
这些数据甚至可以输入f
thirty five's augmented reality helmet
三十五的增强现实头盔
so the pilots of f thirty fives can
所以f35的飞行员可以
see things no other pilots can see
看到其他飞行员看不到的东西
so
所以
the us already has a pretty robust missile defense system
美国已经拥有相当强大的导弹防御系统
but the executive order for the golden dome seeks to
但是金穹顶的行政命令试图
increase the coverage of this system significantly
显着增加该系统的覆盖范围
and the order contains one specific line
订单包含一行特定的行
that brings more questions than answers
这带来的问题比答案多
it states that the golden Dome should
它说金色穹顶应该
protect against countervalue threats
防范反价值威胁
a countervalue threat refers to an attack aimed at targets
反价值威胁是指针对目标的攻击
with high civilian economic or cultural importance
具有高度的民用经济或文化重要性的
such as cities
如城市
industrial centers
工业中心
or infrastructure
或基础设施
the goal is not to disable military forces directly
目标不是直接让军队失去战斗力
but to cause maximum psychological
而是要引起最大的心理
economic or human damage
经济或人身损害
this marks a shift in priorities from protecting
这标志着优先事项从保护
military assets to defending civilians directly
军事资产直接保护平民
instead of covering the entire country
而不是覆盖整个国家
the plan adds an extra layer of
该计划增加了一层额外的
protection around major cities
主要城市周边防护
this means it's now the government's
这意味着它现在是政府的
job to start adding priorities
开始添加优先级的工作
which cities will be covered
将覆盖哪些城市
what criteria determines whether
什么标准决定是否
extra protection is needed
需要额外的保护
is it population size  if so
如果是这样，是人口规模吗？
what's the threshold
门槛是多少？
one million  maybe less
一百万也许更少
you might not hear about it
你可能没听说过
but one day
但是有一天
a missile defense system could
导弹防御系统可以
quietly appear in a city near you
悄然出现在你附近的城市
this approach is similar to the iron dome
这种做法类似于铁穹
designed to protect specific areas during
旨在保护特定区域
the final moments of an incoming attack
即将到来的攻击的最后时刻
Thad handles high altitude threats from long range
萨德处理来自远程的高空威胁
but it's not effective at stopping low flying missiles
但它不能有效阻止低空飞行的导弹
drones or cruise missiles
无人机或巡航导弹
that's where the patriot system comes in
这就是爱国者系统的用武之地
covering the lower altitude layer and
覆盖低海拔层和
providing a final shield for high risk targets
为高风险目标提供最后的保护
like TAD and Aegis
就像TAD和Aegis一样
the patriot uses a phased array radar
爱国者用的是相控阵雷达
what sets it apart is its ability to
它与众不同的是它能够
use different types of interceptors
使用不同类型的拦截器
the PAC three relies on direct
PAC三依靠直接
impact to destroy incoming missiles
撞击摧毁来袭导弹
while the PAC two detonates near the target
而PAC 2在目标附近引爆
creating a cloud of high speed fragments to take it down
制造出一团高速碎片来摧毁它
in Ukraine  Patriot systems have played a key role in
在乌克兰，爱国者系统在
intercepting both ballistic and cruise missiles
拦截弹道导弹和巡航导弹
adding a critical layer to the country's air defense
为国家的防空增加了一个关键层
but these systems are expensive to
但是这些系统很贵
operate and their coverage is limited
操作，覆盖范围有限
each PAC-3 missile costs nearly four million dollars
每枚PAC-3导弹的成本接近400万美元
so while the system is highly effective
所以虽然系统非常有效
every launch has to be carefully considered
每次发射都必须仔细考虑
these systems are all technically mobile
这些系统在技术上都是移动的
but they can't move quickly
但他们不能快速行动
this is where the f thirty five comes in to fill the gap
这就是f35填补空白的地方
more than just a fighter jet
不仅仅是一架战斗机
it acts as a highly mobile node in
它充当高度移动的节点
that digital battlefield map
那个数字战场地图
and it can perform every step of the process too
它也可以执行过程的每一步
with its radar
用它的雷达
the f-35 can detect missile launches in
f-35可以探测到导弹发射
ways that stationary systems cannot
固定系统无法做到的方式
it can pick up heat signatures of a missile engine
它能探测到导弹引擎的热信号
the faint radar trail of a low flying cruise missile
低空飞行的巡航导弹的微弱雷达跟踪
or even the shockwave of a hypersonic
甚至是高超音速的冲击波
vehicle traveling at high speed
高速行驶的车辆
because it can fly close or even inside contested airspace
因为它可以靠近甚至在有争议的空域内飞行
it can detect and track these threats
它可以检测和跟踪这些威胁
earlier than ground based systems ever could
比地面系统更早
but the f thirty five does not
但f 35没有
just stop at seeing the threat
只要停止看到威胁
it shares what it knows
它分享它所知道的
in the golden dome framework this aircraft becomes a flying
在金色穹顶框架中，这架飞机变成了一架飞行的飞机
command post using encrypted data links to transmit live
指挥所使用加密数据链进行实时传输
tracking data to other systems and if needed the f thirty
跟踪数据到其他系统，如果需要，f 30
five can do more than just pass the message along
五个人可以做的不仅仅是传递信息
it can take the shot
它可以开枪
equipped with air to air missiles
装备有空对空导弹
it has the ability to engage and
它有能力参与和
destroy missiles mid flight
摧毁飞行中的导弹
future upgrades may go even further integrating
未来的升级可能会进一步集成
high energy lasers that could target threats
可以瞄准威胁的高能激光
without relying on traditional interceptors
不依赖传统的拦截器
that means fast
这意味着快
flexible response options against drones
针对无人机的灵活响应选项
cruise missiles
巡航导弹
or even high speed threats
甚至高速威胁
all of these technologies already existed
所有这些技术都已经存在
but where things get truly controversial is
但真正有争议的是
where the golden dome executive order
金色穹顶行政命令
demands new technologies to be deployed
需要部署新技术
these systems all have one major weakness
这些系统都有一个主要弱点
they all target the threat after the boost phase
他们都在助推阶段后瞄准威胁
and because of that
正因为如此
one line in the executive order stands out most
行政命令中最突出的一行
the order demands congress to fund the development
该命令要求国会资助开发
and deployment of capabilities to defeat missile
和部署击败导弹的能力
attacks prior to launch and in the boost phase
发射前和助推阶段的攻击
that means golden dome will need
这意味着金色穹顶需要
global interceptor coverage
全球拦截器覆盖范围
and that requires the us to cross a
这需要美国越过一个
line that many do not want crossed
许多人不想跨越的界限
weapons in space
太空武器
the only way to guarantee a successful boost phase
保证助推阶段成功的唯一方法
interception anywhere in the world is to deploy a
世界任何地方的拦截都是为了部署一个
constellation of interceptors in low earth orbit
近地轨道拦截星群
ready to respond instantly to any launch
准备好立即响应任何发射
it's the only approach with the speed and coverage
这是唯一有速度和覆盖范围的方法
needed to stop a missile at its most vulnerable moment
需要在导弹最脆弱的时候阻止它
this has been proposed before
这之前已经提出过了
Reagan wanted to do it during the cold war and
冷战期间里根就想这么做
introduce projects that were never launched like
介绍从未启动过的项目，例如
rods from god and Brilliant pebbles
来自上帝的棒和辉煌的鹅卵石
but things have changed since the eighties
但自从80年代以来情况发生了变化
mainly the launch cost per
主要是每
kilogram has decreased drastically
公斤急剧减少
however this is still the most
然而，这仍然是最
uncertain part of the proposed system
拟议系统的不确定部分
we don't know exactly what kind of
我们不知道具体是什么样的
interceptors would be deployed in space
拦截器将部署在太空中
how they would operate
他们将如何运作
or how effectively they could engage
或者他们如何有效地参与
a missile in the boost phase
处于助推阶段的导弹
or perhaps most importantly
或者也许最重要的是
how the world would react to weapons being placed in space
世界将如何应对放置在太空的武器
to provide global coverage the satellite
为卫星提供全球覆盖
constellation would need to be large
星座需要很大
estimates range from one thousand three hundred to
估计从一千三百到
two thousand satellites in low earth orbit
近地轨道两千颗卫星
while this was deemed too
虽然这也被认为是
expensive in the nineteen eighties
二十世纪八十年代贵的
this is now not just feasible
这现在不仅仅是可行的
it's already been done
已经完成了
starlink already has seven thousand satellites in orbit
Starlink已经有七千颗卫星在轨道上运行
however  an interceptor satellite would be more complex and
然而拦截卫星会更复杂
expensive than any communication satellite
比任何通信卫星都贵
the working mechanism of the
工作机制
interceptors is still up for debate
拦截器仍有争议
but we can look to the past to guess
但我们可以回顾过去来猜测
what the future might look like
未来会是什么样子
brilliant pebbles was proposed in the nineteen eighties
辉煌鹅卵石是在20世纪80年代提出的
consisting of a central kinetic strike vehicle
由中央动力攻击车组成
surrounded by fuel and oxidizer tanks that would
被燃料和氧化剂罐包围
power the weapon to its target before falling away
让武器在坠落前击中目标
in orbit  the interceptor would have remained inside a
在轨道上，拦截器会留在
protective shell called a life jacket
称为救生衣的保护壳
which included solar panels
其中包括太阳能电池板
a star tracker and a laser communication system
星跟踪器和激光通信系统
the project was cancelled during bill clinton's
该项目在比尔克林顿执政期间被取消
presidency due to inadequate funding
因资金不足而担任总统
putting what are essentially air to air missiles in space
向太空发射空空导弹
would not go down well in the international community
在国际社会不会很受欢迎
especially as there is no guarantee the us
尤其是因为不能保证美国
wouldn't use them for offensive purposes
不会把它们用于攻击性目的
but perhaps there is a less
但也许还有更少的
egregious way to achieve this goal
实现这一目标的异乎寻常的方式
lasers  lasers destroy targets by focusing high
激光通过高度聚焦摧毁目标
energy beams of light onto a small area
能量光束投射到一个小区域
rapidly heating the surface until it weakens
迅速加热表面直到它变弱
melts or explodes
熔化或爆炸
this process can disable critical components
此过程可以禁用关键组件
like guidance systems or fuel tanks
比如导航系统或油箱
causing the missile to break apart or veer off course
导致导弹解体或偏离航线
with the energy traveling at the speed of light
能量以光速传播
it allows for near instant engagement
它允许近乎即时的参与
once the laser is aimed and locked on
一旦激光瞄准并锁定
incredibly useful for fast moving hypersonic targets
对快速移动的高超音速目标非常有用
the us has already tested an airborne high powered
美国已经测试了一种机载大功率
laser attached to a Boeing seven four seven
激光连接到波音747上
the system successfully demonstrated its ability to
该系统成功地展示了其能力
shoot down ballistic missiles in the boost phase by
通过以下方式击落助推阶段的弹道导弹
heating and rupturing the structure mid flight
在飞行中加热并破坏结构
so instead of shooting down missiles with other missiles
所以与其用其他导弹击落导弹
these satellites could include
这些卫星可能包括
lasers to burn up missiles instead  however
然而，激光烧毁导弹
the system would need a lot of power
这个系统需要很大的能量
the u s navy's Helios laser installed on the
美国海军的太阳神激光器安装在
uss preble is a sixty kilowatt laser
Preble号是60千瓦的激光器
but that's the output power
但那是输出功率
not the power draw
不是权力抽签
it's expected that a space bound laser would need anywhere
预计太空激光需要任何地方
between two hundred and fifty kilowatts to one megawatt
在二百五十千瓦到一兆瓦之间
two hundred and fifty kilowatts is around the
二百五十千瓦大约是
maximum power generation of the international
国际最大发电量
space station's massive solar arrays
空间站的大型太阳能电池阵列
but their average power barely
但他们的平均力量
satisfies half that power need
满足一半的电力需求
and we would need thousands of these in low earth orbit
我们在近地轨道上需要成千上万个这样的东西。
however  with launch costs lowering
然而，随着发射成本的降低
there are several companies right now that want to
现在有几家公司想
place massive solar arrays in geosynchronous orbit
将大型太阳能电池板置于地球同步轨道
and then transfer that power from these
然后从这些地方转移能量
centralized solar arrays to where it's needed
将太阳能电池板集中到需要的地方
using microwaves with much higher power densities
使用功率密度更高的微波
so in theory a secondary power layer constellation at a
因此，理论上，次级功率层星座在a
higher orbit could allow these satellites to be smaller
更高的轨道可以让这些卫星更小
operating at lower standby power settings until the laser is
在较低的待机功率设置下运行，直到激光
needed at which time power could be directed to them
在那个时候权力可以被引导到他们身上
but needless to say
但不用说
this isn't going to be a popular solution either
这也不会是一个受欢迎的解决方案
experts question whether such a complex
专家质疑这样的复杂
global missile defense system can
全球导弹防御系统可以
realistically be built on the proposed timeline
实际上建立在提议的时间表之上
the initial budget estimate of one hundred and
初步预算估计一百零一
seventy five billion is already being challenged
750亿人口已经面临挑战。
other more realistic budgets project the
其他更现实的预算预测
cost could exceed five hundred and forty two
成本可能超过542
billion over the next twenty years
在接下来的二十年里
raising concerns about long term feasibility and funding
提出对长期可行性和资金的担忧
at a time when major political
在主要政治
battles are being waged over us debt
围绕美国债务的斗争正在展开
including between the primary launch
包括在主要发射之间
provider ceo and the president
供应商首席执行官和总裁
the project's first twenty five billion is tied to a
该项目的前250亿美元与
broader one hundred and fifty billion defense package
更广泛的1500亿国防计划
which is still making its way through congress
该法案仍在国会通过
without that funding
没有这笔资金
the golden dome could face early delays or scaling back
金色穹顶可能面临早期延误或缩减
just as it did in the nineteen nineties
就像19世纪90年代一样
there are also geopolitical risks
还有地缘政治风险
China has strongly objected
中国强烈反对
warning that the golden dome has offensive
警告金色穹顶有攻击性
implications and could trigger an arms race in space
可能引发太空军备竞赛
Russia has echoed those concerns
俄罗斯也表达了同样的担忧
and not to mention
更不用说
these countries have anti satellite weapons and
这些国家有反卫星武器和
are likely willing to use them if needed
如果需要，可能愿意使用它们
which could cut off space for the entire
这可能会切断整个空间
planet if a battle was waged in orbit
如果在轨道上进行战斗
which again  i think we can all agree isn't worth the
我想我们都同意这不值得
cost to start wars none of us want
发动战争的代价我们都不想要
if you are watching this video
如果你正在看这个视频
there is a pretty high chance you're an engineer
你很有可能是个工程师
or you just like free things that are
或者你只是喜欢免费的东西
usually incredibly expensive
通常非常昂贵
but today's video sponsor Onshape is giving
但是今天的视频赞助商Onform
six months of their professional design
六个月的专业设计
software away for free with my link Onshape
使用我的链接Onform免费赠送软件
pro slash realengineering
专业斜杠现实工程
Onshape is fantastic for both robotics
对于两个机器人技术来说，Onform都很棒。
projects and professional level designs
项目和专业水平设计
design software is typically really expensive and can often
设计软件通常非常昂贵，并且通常
require a powerful computer to complete the more processor
需要一台强大的计算机来完成更多的处理器
heavy tasks like finite element analysis and rendering
有限元分析和渲染等繁重任务
i've been using one of my oldest laptops that i've
我一直在用我最旧的笔记本电脑
set up in my garage for my 3d printer
在我的车库里为我的3d打印机设置
and it runs without an issue because
它运行没有问题，因为
it's all done through the cloud
都是通过云端完成的
not locally
非本地的
and it solves other problems too
它也解决了其他问题
like keeping files up to date for
比如让文件保持最新
large engineering and sales teams
大型工程和销售团队
because it's fully cloud based
因为它完全基于云
everyone on your team can access the
您团队中的每个人都可以访问
latest version of a design anytime  anywhere
随时随地设计的最新版本
on any device
在任何设备上
and that would have saved me a ton of headaches
那样我就不会那么头疼了
when i was sending cad files back and forth with
当我来回发送cad文件时
sales teams and suppliers in my old job
我以前工作的销售团队和供应商
on more than one occasion
不止一次
sales teams sent out outdated files  and now
销售团队发送了过时的文件，现在
onshape has launched onshape government
onform已经启动了onform政府
a version of their platform that is itar and ear compliant
他们平台的一个版本，符合吉他和耳朵的要求
making it a viable option for defense contractors and any
使其成为国防承包商和任何
teams working on regulated or export controlled projects
从事受监管或出口管制项目的团队
like a highly secretive military space constellation for
就像一个高度隐秘的军事太空星座
example
例子
whether you're designing complex systems at work or
无论您是在工作中设计复杂的系统还是
building your next robotics project at home
在家中构建您的下一个机器人项目
you can try onshape for free at onshape
您可以免费试用onform
pro slash realengineering or just
专业斜杠现实工程或只是
click the link in the description
点击描述中的链接